## Marielle S. Hsu

marielle.hsu@gmail.com A Berkeley, CA A 704.839.6599

My artistic upbringing instilled a keen eye for aesthetics and creative solutions. Always willing to dig deeper to find the roots of problems, I bring a collection of abilities that open new perspectives, both globally and at the implementation level. I specialize in creative thinking and problem-solving, with a strong emphasis on accuracy and efficiency.

### **Experience:**

## Retail Interaction Designer Other Machine Co.

San Francisco, CA 2013 - 2014

Solely responsible for contents, flow, launch, and monitoring of the web store supporting our portable CNC milling machine. Design and implement packaging, creative kit contents, and customer outreach. Investigate, test, order, and track inventory. Research and report on market trends in the "maker" space across the globe, as well as within small-scale manufacturing. Ensure that all customers have a pleasant and joyful experience.

# Quality Assurance Tester Gree International, Incorporated

San Francisco, CA 2012 - 2013

Conduct black-box testing of mobile games on iOS and Android. Assist with QA sign-off leading up to submission to the Apple App Store and Google Play. Ensure consistency across testcases and bug reports. Mentor new hires. Launched the first NFL-branded game in the iTunes App Store. Solely responsible for all aspects of QA before and after launch for several core features on our Call to Arms (real-time strategy) game.

## Quality Assurance Tester / Lead Songbird / Pioneers of the Inevitable

San Francisco, CA

2009 - 2012

Develop high-level test plan for new products and features. Coordinate testing with both local and remote QA groups via Skype, basecamp, and PivotalTracker. Report on time needed for QA within Agile process. Edit and update Litmus testcases as features change. Handle all aspects of QA on desktop and Android for specific features within each release. Assist with community engagement via GetSatisfaction, facebook, and Twitter. Maintain an orderly and useful bug database in bugzilla.

#### Systems Administrator Xantrion Consulting

Oakland, CA

2009

Certified HDI Customer Service Representative. Remote server administration, on-site customer support, and finance planning for small to medium businesses.

# Department Secretary / Administrative Assistant III University of California, Berkeley

Berkeley, CA

2008

Managed logistics, finances, supplies, information flow, and technology assistance for faculty, Teaching Assistants, and graduate students in the Electrical Engineering and Computer Science departments.

### Information Technology Intern Blair Dubilier & Associates

Bethesda, MD

2006

Installing and updating hardware and software for interactive exhibits at the Geppi Entertainment Museum (Baltimore, MD), the National Portrait Gallery (Washington, DC), and the National Library of Medicine (Bethesda, MD). Emergency fire response procedures.

### **Education:**

Bryn Mawr College University of St Andrews University of California, Berkeley Bachelors degree in Physics Semester abroad in Physics and CS Mandarin Chinese intensive summer series

Bryn Mawr, PA Scotland Berkeley, CA

## Other Skills and Interests:

- ▲ Working knowledge of MLA and Chicago Manual of Style.
- Contributing member of the Cal Sailing Club.
- Assisted with Ardent Heavy Industries art projects and installations at events around the Western US.
- ▲ CREATE member of the blacksmithing workshop, and Fire Safety Volunteer at The Crucible in West Oakland.
- On-site resource and Cultural Ambassador at Shades of Blues partner dance venue in San Francisco.
- Meeting Chair for national dance event BluesQuake 2014 and planning committee for BluesQuake 2015.
- Founding board member of the Golden Gate Blues non-profit, established to provide continued access to quality blues music and dance classes in the Bay Area. Operates the longest-running blues dance venue in the country.